President, Office of the; Records ua000
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Office of Abram Brubacher Records, 1904-1930; 2; 14.8
  - Alphabetic File - V, 1925-1926 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Alphabetic File - WA, 1925-1926 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Alphabetic File - WL, 1925-1926 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Alphabetic File - Wh, 1925-1926 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Alphabetic File - Wia - Wil, 1925-1926 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - Alphabetic File - Wim - Wiz, 1925-1926 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Alphabetic File - WO-WZ, 1925-1926 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Alphabetic File - Z, 1925-1926 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Alumni Records, 1925-1926 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Appointments, 1925-1926 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Bucket File, 1925-1926 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Faculty Application, 1925-1926 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Faculty Application, 1925-1926 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - Faculty Application, 1925-1926 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - President's Annual Report of the New York State College for teachers, 1925-1926 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Speaking Engagements, 1925-1926 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - Library School, 1925-1934 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - Commencement, 1926 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 18)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1926 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 19)
  - Normal Schools, 1926 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 20)
  - Normal Schools, 1926 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 21)
  - Normal Schools, 1926 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 22)
  - President's Annual Report of the New York State College for teachers, 1926 December 3 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 23)
  - Quakenbush Weil, 1926 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 24)
  - Report The State Department of Education, 1926 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 25)
  - "Student Demonstration in Legislature", 1926 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 26)
  - Alphabetic File - Aa-Ai, 1926-1927 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 27)
  - Alphabetic File - Ai-Al, 1926-1927 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 28)
  - Alphabetic File - Am-Ar, 1926-1927 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 29)
  - Alphabetic File - As-Ay, 1926-1927 (Box 17 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 30)
  - Alphabetic File - BAP-BAR, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Alphabetic File - BAS-BAZ, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Alphabetic File - Be-Bh, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Alphabetic File - Bi-Bl, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Alphabetic File - Bo-Bq, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - Alphabetic File - Bra-Bri, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Alphabetic File - Bro-Bry, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Alphabetic File - Bu-By, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Alphabetic File - CA-Cd, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Alphabetic File - Cl-Cl, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Alphabetic File - COA-CON, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Alphabetic File - C, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Alphabetic File - Cr-Ct, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - Alphabetic File - Cu-Cy, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - Alphabetic File - Convocation, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Alphabetic File - DA-De, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - Alphabetic File - Di-Do, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - Alphabetic File - Dr-Dy, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 18)
  - Alphabetic File - EA-EN, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 19)
  - Alphabetic File - Eo-Ey, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 20)
  - Alphabetic File - FA-Fi, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 21)
  - Alphabetic File - Fl-Fo, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 22)
  - Alphabetic File - Fr-Fy, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 23)
  - Alphabetic File - GA-Ge, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 24)
  - Alphabetic File - Gi-Go, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 25)
  - Alphabetic File - GR-Gy, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 26)
  - Alphabetic File - HAA-HAN, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 27)
  - Alphabetic File - HAR-HAY, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 28)
  - Alphabetic File - He, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 29)
  - Alphabetic File - Hi, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 30)
  - Alphabetic File - Ho, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 31)
  - Alphabetic File - Hu-Hy, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 32)
  - Alphabetic File - I, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 33)
  - Alphabetic File - J, 1926-1927 (Box 18 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 34)
  - Alphabetic File - KA-Ke, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Alphabetic File - Ki-Ko, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Alphabetic File - Kr-Ky, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Alphabetic File - LA, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Alphabetic File - Le, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - Alphabetic File - Li-Ly, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Alphabetic File - McA-McD, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Alphabetic File - McE-McK, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Alphabetic File - McL-McZ, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Alphabetic File - MA, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Alphabetic File - Me-Mi, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Alphabetic File - Mo-Mu, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Alphabetic File - My, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - Alphabetic File - Na-Ni, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - Alphabetic File - No-Ny, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Alphabetic File - O, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - Alphabetic File - PA-Pe, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - Alphabetic File - Pi-Po, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 18)
  - Alphabetic File - Pr-Py, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 19)
  - Alphabetic File - Ra-Re, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 20)
  - Alphabetic File - Ri-Rod, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 21)
  - Alphabetic File - Rog-Ruz, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 22)
  - Alphabetic File - Sa-Sca, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 23)
  - Alphabetic File - Sch-Scy, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 24)
  - Alphabetic File - Se-Sha, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 25)
  - Alphabetic File - Si-Smi, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 26)
  - Alphabetic File - So, Sp, Sq, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 27)
  - Alphabetic File - Sta-Ste, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 28)
  - Alphabetic File - Sti-Sty, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 29)
  - Alphabetic File - Su-Sy, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 30)
  - Alphabetic File - Ta, Te, Ti, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 31)
  - Alphabetic File - To, Tr, Tu, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 32)
  - Alphabetic File - U, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 33)
  - Alphabetic File - V, 1926-1927 (Box 19 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 34)
  - Alphabetic File - Wa, 1926-1927 (Box 20 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Alphabetic File - We, 1926-1927 (Box 20 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Alphabetic File - Wie-Wil, 1926-1927 (Box 20 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Alphabetic File - Wim-Wiz, 1926-1927 (Box 20 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Alphabetic File - Wo-Wy, 1926-1927 (Box 20 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - Alphabetic File - Y, 1926-1927 (Box 20 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Alphabetic File - Z, 1926-1927 (Box 20 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Alphabetic File - Alumni File, 1926-1927 (Box 20 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Alphabetic File - American Association of University Women, 1926-1927 (Box 20 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Alphabetic File - American College Bureau, 1926-1927 (Box 20 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Alphabetic File - Attendance, 1926-1927 (Box 20 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Alphabetic File - Bulletins, 1926-1927 (Box 20 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Departmental Reports - Library School, 1926-1927 (Box 20 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - Alphabetic File - Economics of Government Department, 1926-1927 (Box 20 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - Alphabetic File - Educational Psychology, 1926-1927 (Box 20 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Alphabetic File - French Department, 1926-1927 (Box 21 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - Alphabetic File - English department, 1926-1927 (Box 20 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - Harmon Student Loan Fund, 1926-1927 (Box 20 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 18)
  - Harmon Student Loan Fund, 1926-1927 (Box 20 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 19)
  - Alphabetic File - Home Economics Department, 1926-1927 (Box 20 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 20)
  - Legislative File, 1926-1927 (Box 20 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 21)
  - Alphabetic File - Library School, 1926-1927 (Box 20 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 22)
  - Alphabetic File - Material on Admissions, 1926-1927 (Box 20 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 23)
  - Alphabetic File - Mathematics Department Vacancy, 1926-1927 (Box 20 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 24)
  - PAN American Union, 1926-1927 (Box 21 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Performance of Graduates, 1926-1927 (Box 21 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1926-1927 (Box 21 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - President's Annual Report of the New York State College for teachers, 1926-1927 (Box 21 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Alphabetic File - Re: Miss Avery 1927, 1926-1927 (Box 21 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - President's Office - Board of Trustees, 1926-1928 (Box 21 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - President's office - Budget, 1927 (Box 21 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Decker Corresspondence, 1927 (Box 21 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - President's Annual Report of the New York State College for teachers, 1927 December (Box 21 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Publications "The Next Step in Education in the United States", 1927 (Box 21 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Summer Session, 1927 (Box 21 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Alphabetic File - LA, 1927-1928 (Box 21 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Alphabetic File - Le, 1927-1928 (Box 21 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - Alphabetic File - Li-Ly, 1927-1928 (Box 21 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - Alphabetic File - MA, 1927-1928 (Box 21 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Alphabetic File - McA-McD, 1927-1928 (Box 21 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - Alphabetic File - McE-McK, 1927-1928 (Box 21 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - Alphabetic File - Mch-McZ, 1927-1928 (Box 21 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 18)
  - Alphabetic File - MO-MU, 1927-1928 (Box 21 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 19)
  - Alphabetic File - My, 1927-1928 (Box 21 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 20)
  - Alphabetic File - NA-Ni, 1927-1928 (Box 21 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 21)
  - Alphabetic File - NO-Ny, 1927-1928 (Box 21 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 22)
  - Alphabetic File - O, 1927-1928 (Box 21 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 23)
  - Alphabetic File - PA-Pc, 1927-1928 (Box 21 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 24)
  - Alphabetic File - Pi-Po, 1927-1928 (Box 21 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 25)
  - Alphabetic File - Pr-Py, 1927-1928 (Box 21 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 26)
  - Alphabetic File - Q, 1927-1928 (Box 21 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 27)
  - Alphabetic File - Ra-Re, 1927-1928 (Box 22 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Alphabetic File - Ri-Rod, 1927-1928 (Box 22 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Alphabetic File - Rog-Ruz, 1927-1928 (Box 22 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Alphabetic File - S, 1927-1928 (Box 22 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Alphabetic File - Sch-Scy, 1927-1928 (Box 22 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - Alphabetic File - Se-Sha, 1927-1928 (Box 22 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Alphabetic File - She-Shy, 1927-1928 (Box 22 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Alphabetic File - Si-Smi, 1927-1928 (Box 22 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Alphabetic File - So-Sq, 1927-1928 (Box 22 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Alphabetic File - STA-STl, 1927-1928 (Box 22 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Alphabetic File - Sti-Sty, 1927-1928 (Box 22 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Alphabetic File - Su-Sy, 1927-1928 (Box 22 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Alphabetic File - TA-Ti, 1927-1928 (Box 22 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - President's Office - Appointments Professional, 1927-1928 (Box 22 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - President's office - correspondence, 1927-1928 (Box 22 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - President's Office - connes- A, 1927-1928 (Box 22 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - President's Office - connes- Ba-Be, 1927-1928 (Box 22 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - President's Office - connes- Bi-By, 1927-1928 (Box 22 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 18)
  - President's Office - connes- Ca-CL, 1927-1928 (Box 22 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 19)
  - President's Office - connes- Co-Cy, 1927-1928 (Box 22 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 20)
  - President's Office - connes- D, 1927-1928 (Box 22 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 21)
  - President's Office - connes- E-F, 1927-1928 (Box 22 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 22)
  - President's Office - connes- G, 1927-1928 (Box 22 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 23)
  - President's Office - connes- Frank Graves, 1925-1928 (Box 22 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 24)
  - President's Office - connes- Haa-Han, 1927-1928 (Box 23 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - President's Office - connes- Han-Hy, 1927-1928 (Box 23 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - President's Office - connes- I-K, 1927-1928 (Box 23 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - President's Office - connes- To-Tu, 1927-1928 (Box 23 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - President's Office - connes- U-V, 1927-1928 (Box 23 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - President's Office - connes- W, 1927-1928 (Box 23 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - President's Office - connes- Wiley, George, 1927-1928 (Box 23 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - President's Office - connes- Y, 1927-1928 (Box 23 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - President's Office - Freshman Registration, 1927-1928 (Box 23 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - President's Office - "High School" English, 1927-1928 (Box 23 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1927-1928 (Box 23 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Psychological Testing, 1927-1928 (Box 23 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Soroities, 1927-1928 (Box 23 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - Speaking Engagements, 1927-1928 (Box 23 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - American Association of Teacher's Colleges, 1927-1939 (Box 23 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - President's Office - Applications Professional, 1928 (Box 24 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - President's Office - Buffalo Normal School -Name Change, 1928 (Box 24 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Publications - "State Education Department Hs Administrative Judicial Tribunals, 1928 (Box 24 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Round Table Conference, 1928 (Box 24 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - State College Faculty Member - Personal Scholastic dates, 1928 (Box 24 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - President's Annual Report of the New York State College for teachers, 1928-1930 (Box 24 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - President's Report Biennial, 1928-1930 (Box 24 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Selective Admission Tests, 1928-1933 (Box 24 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Master's Thesis and Graduate Study, 1928-1937 (Box 24 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Teacher Training, 1928-1938 (Box 24 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Faculty Committee on Student Personnel, 1928-1939 (Box 24 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - History of State College, 1844-1939 (Box 24 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Addresses, etc. "Anxious Parents and College Freshman", 1929 (Box 24 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - Addresses, etc. "Corner Stone Laying of the Albany Academy", 1929 (Box 24 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - Addresses, etc. "The College at Work", 1929 (Box 24 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Addresses, etc. "Why Teacher's Fail", 1929 (Box 24 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - Memorende File, 1929 (Box 24 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - President's Office Report on Curriculum and School Organization, 1929 (Box 24 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 18)
  - Budgeting Material - State College, 1929-1930 (Box 25 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Index to Reports, 1929-1930 (Box 25 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Commissioner's Grades, 1929-1930 (Box 25 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - E, 1929-1934 (Box 25 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - NEA, C (National Education association) Study on adjusting teaching supply to demand, 1929; 1931; 1933; 1935 (Box 25 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - General, 1929-1936 (Box 25 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Simpson, A.D Commissioner of Finance, 1929-1937 (Box 25 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - American Association of Teacher's Colleges, 1929-1938 (Box 25 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - The Volume Library, 1929-1933; 1935-1936; 1938 (Box 25 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - T, 1929-1939 (Box 25 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Miscellionerus, 1929-1939 (Box 25 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Office of the President Resignation, 1929-1958 (Box 25 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Office of the President Resignation, 1929-1958 (Box 25 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - Departmental Reports Summer Session, 1930 (Box 25 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - Husted Fellowship Fund, history and financial information, 1930 (Box 25 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Alphabetic File - M, 1930-1931 (Box 25 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - Alphabetic File - Y, 1930-1931 (Box 25 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - Hayes, Margret - Report, 1930-1931 (Box 26 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - President's Report, 1930-1931 (Box 26 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - President's Report of the New York State College for Teachers, 1930-1931 (Box 26 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - President's Office - Annual Report, 1930-1933 (Box 26 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - American Association of University Women, 1930-1934 (Box 26 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - Annual Report of board of trustees, 1930-1934 (Box 26 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Foreign Students, 1930-1931; 1935 (Box 26 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Educators Association, 1930-1937 (Box 26 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Wiley, Dr. g.m, 1930-1937 (Box 26 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Correspondence File - H, 1930-1938 (Box 26 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Writings and Publications, 1930-1934; 1937-1938 (Box 26 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Board of Regents, 1930-1939 (Box 26 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Budget File, 1930-1939 (Box 26 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)